whatabeautifullife.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy details how your personal information is collected and how your personal information may be used. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any web site not operated by us.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

**1\. Information Collection**

We collect information from you in several different ways. One goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience.

**2\. Information Use and Disclosure**

(a) Internal Use. We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service and also may share your information with affiliates under the company's control.

(b) Communications with You. We will use your personal information to communicate with you. Also, we may send you a confirmation email when you register with us. We may send you a service-related announcement on the rare occasions when it is necessary.

(c) External Use. We want to provide you with excellent service and to offer you a great selection. We do not sell, rent, trade, license or otherwise disclose your specific personal information or financial information to anyone other than to affiliates under the company's control.

**Choice and Opt-Out**

If you no longer wish to receive the Company's promotional communications, you may "opt-out" of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by e-mailing the Company at service@whatabeautifullife.com.

**UPDATES TO THIS POLICY**

If we change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post changes and updates on the site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use and disclose. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated.
